

PHD STUDENT . SOFTWARE ENGINEER

585 Purdue Mall ME3171, West Lafayette, IN 47907

□ (415)203-8543 | ☑ chi45@purdue.edu | ♠ hyung-gun.me | □ stnoah1 | □ hyung-gun | ➢ Hyung-gun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie at the intersection of Computer Vision and Robotics, focusing on 3D Geometric Deep Learning and Temporal Action Anaylsis. In this area, I apply Machine/Deep Learning algorithms for Augmented/Virtual Reality and Video.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

PHD IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2018 - PRESENT Seoul, South Korea

Yonsei University

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Mar. 2010 - Feb. 2017

Skills_

Language Python, Matlab, C/C++, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP

Machine/Deep Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow, Keras

Web Programming MYSQL/mongoDB, Flask/Node.js

ETC GAZEBO, ROS, SolidWorks, AutoCAD

Publications

Conference Proceedings

- [C2] A Large-scale Mechanical Components Benchmark for Deep Neural Networks. In proceedings of the 16th European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020.
- [C1] First-Person View Hand Segmentation of Multi-Modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. In proceedings of the 31st British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2020.

Journal Papers

- [J3] Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations. In Computer-Aided Design (2020): 102932.
- [J2] Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. In *The Visual Computer* (2019): 1-15.
- [J1] An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification. In *Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST)* 33, no. 3 (2019): 1333-1339.

Research Experience

Weakly-Supervised Temporal Action Localization

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

May. 2020 - Present

- · Proposed a novel architecture to localize temporal boundaries of action in untrimmed videos when only given action order.
- · Formulated action localization problem as a sequence translation problem and applied Transformer Architecture.

A Large-scale Mechanical Component Benchmark Dataset [C2]

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Feb. 2019 - Mar. 2020

- Introduced a large-scale mechanical components benchmark for the classification and retrieval tasks.
- Developed a data collecting pipeline including annotation interface and database.

Hand segmentation with RGBD-T data [C1]

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Jul. 2019 - May. 2020

- · Proposed a novel hand video dataset with RGB, Depth, and Themral images for hand segmentation.
- Developed a method which segment hands and objects with a multi-modal Deep Neural network dealing with RGBD-T data.

Part Geometry Net (PGNet) [J3]

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Oct. 2018 - Aug. 2019

- Proposed a Generative Adversarial Network (GAN) that synthesize 3D objects given a discrete category condition and continuous instance-level attributes by fusing the various types of geometric information.
- Consturcted a part identifier module which learns part geometry to preserve part properties of 3D objects.

Latent Transformation Neural Network (LTNN) [J2]

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - April. 2019

- Proposed a fully-convolutional conditional generative network which is capable of view synthesis using a light-weight neural network suited for real-time applications.
- Developed conditional transformation unit which is designed to learn the latent space transformations corresponding to specified target views.